Guide to the Craig Keyzer collection, 1955-1987 MS 972
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Craig Keyzer collection
1955-1987
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Keyzer, Craig
MS 972
1.5 Linear Feet (1 oversized box, 1 box)
This collection consists of fliers, issues of Public News, and concert recordings on CD.
Biographical / Historical
When he lived in Houston, Craig Keyzer was a graphic artist for the alt weekly "Public News." A lover of popular music he collected Houston concert recordings ranging from Elvis and The Beatles to Townes van Zandt.
Content Description
This collection mainly consists of fliers, 88 issues of Public News, and concert recordings on CD.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Craig Keyzer in April 2021.
Related Materials
Public News has been digitized and is available at: https://texashistory.unt.edu/search/?q=%22public+news%22&t=fulltext
Index Terms
Subjects
Folk music; Folk music -- Texas -- Houston; Music
Subjects (Persons)
Keyzer, Craig
- Series I: General files
  - "Fitz Flyer", 1983-05 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fliers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Juneteenth Blues Festival programs, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series II: CDs
  - The Beatles Sam Houston Colosseum Houston, Texas and The Thirteenth Floor Elevators La Maison Club Houston, Texas, 1965-08-19-1966 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Tracks include: "Twist and Shout", "She's a Woman", "I Feel Fine", "Dizzy Miss Lizzie", "Ticket to Ride", "Everybody's Tring to Be My Baby", "Can't Buy Me Love", "Baby's in Black", "I Wanna Be Your Man", "A Hard Day's Night", "Help!", "I'm Down", "Levitation", "Rollercoaster", "Fire Engine", "Reverberation", "Don't Fall Down", "Tried to Hide", "Splash 1", "You're Gonna Miss Me", "Monkey Island Kingdom of Heaven", "She Lives in a Time of Her Own".
  - 2 CDs: Townes Van Zandt Rockefeller's, Houston, Texas, 1984-07-15
    Tracks include: "Coretta", "Just Lookin' For You", "Jokes", "Pancho and Lefty", "Gone, Gone, Blues", "I Ain't Leaving Your Love", "Snowin' on Raton", "Racing in the Streets", "The Catfish Song", "Brand New Companion", "If I Needed You", "La-La-La-Lee, Please Lend Me Your Hand", "The Dollar Bill Blues", "Rex's Blues", "Buckskin Stallion Blues", "Who Do You Love", "The Pueblo Wlatz", "Short-Haired Woman Blues", "You Win Again", "Waitin' Around to Die", "A Lover of Women", "Go Down, Darling", "Maria", "White Firefighter Blues"
  - Elvis Presley Houston Livestock Show and Rodeo The Astrodome Houston, Texas, 1974-03-03
    Tracks include: "See, See Rider", "I Got a Woman", "Love Me", "Trying to Get to You", "All Shook Up", "Love Me Tender", "Johnny B. Goode", "Hound Dog", "Fever", "Polksalad Annie", "Why Me, Lord?", "Suspicious Minds", "I Can't Stop Loving You", "Help Me", "How Great Thou Art", "Let Me Be There", "Funny How Time Slips Away", "Can't Help Falling in Love"
  - Townes Van Zandt Kerville Folk Festival, Kerville, Texas, 1986-05-24
    Tracks include: "Loretta", "Gone, Gone Blues", "I Ain't Leaving Your Love", "Talking Thunderbird Blues", "Pancho and Lefty", "Snowin' on Raton", "The Last Thing on My Mind", "If I Needed You"
  - Townes Van Zandt, Hermann Park, Houston, Texas, The Loading Chute, Houston, Texas, 1984-04-21-1984-05-20
    Tracks include: "Pancho and Lefty", "Just Lookin' for You", "Gone, Gone Blues", "I Ain't Leaving Your Love", "Racing in the Streets", "If I Needed You", "Interview", "Racing in the Streets", "Interview", "If I Needed You", "Slowin' on Raton", "Interview", "Girl Scout Cookies", "Interview", "Oval Room"
  - Roy Orbison, Rockefeller's, Houston, Texas, The Judy's, The Agora, Houston, Texas, 1981-05-16-1987-01-01
    Tracks include: "Only the Lonely", "Leah", "Dream Baby", "In Dreams", "Mean Woman Blues", "Blue Bayou", "Candyman", "Crying", "Oobydooby", "Go, Go, Go", "It's Over", "Pretty Woman", "Running Scared", "Man on a Window Ledge", "Joey (Mechanical Boy)", "Mental Obsession", "Lava of Love", "Washarama", "Get It On Out", "Right Down the Line", "My Imagination", "Dogs", "She's Got the Beat", "Guyana Punch", "Underwater Fun"
  - 2 CD's: Stevie Ray Vaughn and Double Trouble, Fitzgerald's, Houston, Texas, Double Trouble, Juneteenth Blues Festival, Hermann Park, Elvis Presley, Cook's Hoedown Club, 1955-03-20-1983-06-20
    Tracks include: "Be-Bop-A-Lula Opening Jam", "C'mon (Pt. III)", "Mary Had A Little Lamb", "Rude Mood", "Dirty Pool", "Voodoo Child", "Heartfixin' Business", "Driving South", "Texas Flood", "Testify", "Jam #292", "Lenny (End Cut)", "In the Open", "Sugar Coated Love", "I Tried, Pretty Baby", "Collin's Shuffle", "You Can Have My Husband", "My Baby's Gone", "Good Rockin' Tonight", "Baby, Let's Play House", "Blue Moon of Kentucky", "I've Got a Woman", "That's Alright, Mama"
  - Stevie Ray Vaughn and Double Trouble, Fitzgerald's, Houston, Texas, 1981-10-14
    Tracks include: "Boilermaker", "Close to You", "You'll Be Mine", "You Done Lost Your Good Thing Down", "Empty Arms", "Breakdown", "Poison", "Texas Flood", "Rude Mood", "Don't Lose Your Cool", "Hideaway", "Pride in Joy", "Tin Pan Alley", "Letter to My Girlfriend", "Tell Me, Darling", "I Tried, Pretty Baby", "Rude Mood", " Tin Pan Alley", "Close to You", "Breakdown", "Manic Depression", "Don't Lose Your Cool", "The Wham!"
  - 2 CDs Robert Collins, Rockefeller's, Houston, Texas, 1980-06-22-1981-10-11
  - Led Zeppelin, The Summit, Houston, Texas, 1977-05-21
    Track include: "The Song Remains the Same", "Sick Again", "Nobody's Fault but Mine", "In My Time of Dying", "Since I've Been Loving You", "No Quarter", "Ten Years Gone", "The Battle of Evermore", "Going to California", "Black Country Woman", "Bron-Y-Aur Stomp", "White Summer- Black Mountainside", "Kashmir"
  - Led Zeppelin, The Summit, Houston, Texas, 1977-05-21
    Tracks include: "Out on the Tiles- Moby Dick", "Guitar Solo", "Achille's Last Stand", "Stairway to Heaven", "Rock and Roll", "Trampled Underfoot"
  - The Eagles, The Summit, Houston, Texas, The Rolling Stones, Sam Houston Coliseum, Houston, Texas, 1976-11-06-1978-07-19
    Tracks include: "Hotel California", "Lyin' Eyes", "Wasted Time", "Take it Out to the Limit", "Desperado", "Mignight Flyer", "Turn to Stone", "Already Gone", "One of these Nights", "Funk #49", "Good Day in Hell", "Rocky Mountain Way", "Witchy Woman", "James Dean", "The Best of My Love", "Walkaway", "Tequila Sunrise", "All Down the Line", "Honky Tonk Women", "Star, Star", "Lies", "Beast of Burden", "Respectable", "Sweet Little Sixteen", "Brown Sugar", "Jumping Jack Flash"
- Series III: Public News
  - Public News, 88 issues, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
    General
    This has been digitized and is available at: https://texashistory.unt.edu/search/?q=%22public+news%22&t=fulltext
  - Public News flier, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)